



Lateef Mushtaq

Date of birth: 03/10/1997 | **Nationality:** Indian | **Phone number:**

(+49) 17632685486 (Mobile) | Email address: lateefmushtaq4@gmail.com

Website: www.lateefdesigns.com

Address: Arnulfstaße, 113, 12105, Berlin, Germany (Home)

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced UX designer with a successful history of optimizing user experience for startups like Pickrr and Goalwit Technologies and designing interfaces for renowned international companies like Affinidi and Herbalife Nutrition. I also have some experience using ReactJS with Ant Design and Styled Components for developing UI.

WORK EXPERIENCE

01/10/2020 - 01/01/2022 Delhi, India

UX/UI DESIGNER WITS INNOVATION LAB

Collaborated closely with clients and developers, adhering to best practices, and designed interfaces for international companies like Affinidi and Herbalife Nutrition. Delivered user-friendly solutions for startups' complex projects.

Skills: UI/UX Design, Product Design, Wireframes, Prototyping, Information Architecture

01/03/2021 - 31/12/2021 New Delhi, India

UX/UI DESIGNER PICKRR

Improved user experience by simplifying tasks, creating appealing dashboard assets, and integrating new features. Designed Mobile version for important updates and conducted user acceptance testing. Pickrr currently uses my design version.

Skills: UI/UX Design, Product Design, Wireframes, Prototyping, Information Architecture, HTML, CSS.

01/06/2018 - 30/09/2020 New Delhi, India

JUNIOR DESIGNER GOALWIT TECHNOLOGIES

Real-world project experience in designing assets and graphics for Goalwit Technologies' matrimonial startup. Developed the landing page for their product, now used by thousands of users for account creation.

Skills: Graphic Design, User Interface.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/05/2015 - 01/06/2019 New Delhi, India

BACHELOR'S IN COMPUTER SCIENCE Jamia Hamdard University

Website https://jamiahamdard.edu/

01/02/2022 - 01/09/2023 Berlin, Germany

MSC. DATA ANALYTICS Berlin School of Business and Innovation

Website https://www.berlinsbi.com/

DIGITAL SKILLS

UI / UX | Wireframes & Prototyping | Prototyping | Information architecture | User Flow | ReactJS (beginner) | Html, Css, Bootstrap

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **URDU**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

TOOLS

Softwares

Figma • Sketch • Adobe Xd • Adobe PS • Miro • Balsamiq • Jira

CERTIFICATIONS

01/03/2020 - 01/07/2020

Interface Specialization

Online, Coursera, California Arts School (03/2020 - 07/2020)

01/05/2020 - 01/06/2020

Dashboard UI Specialization

Online, Coursera, California Arts School (05/2020 - 06/2020)

01/05/2023 - 01/06/2023

Digital Product Design: UX Research

Online, Udemy

01/09/2023 - 04/10/2023

Instructional Design for ELearning

Online, Udemy